{
    "jokes":[
{
    "question": "Did you hear the one about the guy with the broken hearing aid?", "answer": "Neither did he."
    },
{
    "question": "What do you call a fly without wings?", "answer": "A walk."
    },
{
    "question": "What do you call someone with no nose?", "answer": "Nobody knows."
    },
{
    "question": "What time did the man go to the dentist?", "answer": "Tooth hurt-y."
    },
{
    "question": "Why can’t you hear a pterodactyl go to the bathroom?", "answer": "The p is silent."
    },
{
    "question": "How many optometrists does it take to change a light bulb? 1 or 2?", "answer": "1... or 2?"
    },
{
    "question": "Why does Waldo only wear stripes?", "answer": "Because he doesn't want to be spotted."
    },
{
    "question": "Do you know where you can get chicken broth in bulk?", "answer": "The stock market."
    },
{
    "question": "Why are skeletons so calm?", "answer": "Because nothing gets under their skin."
    },
{
    "question": "Why don’t seagulls fly over the bay?", "answer": "Because then they’d be bay-gulls!"
    },
{
    "question": "What did celery say when he broke up with his girlfriend?", "answer": "She wasn't right for me, so I really don't carrot all."
    },
{
    "question": "What’s 50 Cent’s name in Zimbabwe?", "answer": "400 Million Dollars."
    },
{
    "question": "What's the worst thing about ancient history class?", "answer": "The teachers tend to Babylon."
    },
{
    "joke": "I was thinking about moving to Moscow but there is no point Russian into things."
    },
{
    "joke": "There’s a new type of broom out, it’s sweeping the nation."
    },
{
    "joke": "When my wife told me to stop impersonating a flamingo, I had to put my foot down."
    },
{
    "joke": "I used to work for a soft drink can crusher. It was soda pressing."
    },
{
    "joke": "A ghost walks into a bar and asks for a glass of vodka but the bar tender says, 'sorry we don’t serve spirits'"
    },
{
    "joke": "I went to the zoo the other day, there was only one dog in it. It was a shitzu."
    },
{
    "joke": "I gave all my dead batteries away today, free of charge."
    }]
}